adserve.com 2013-05-21

# AdServe - Privacy Policy

At AdServe we are committed to protecting your privacy. Any information we collect, such as email addresses, is submitted at the visitor's will. We do not and will not share any personal information with any third parties unless by governmental order.

We have NO access to any information collected by our Payment Services providers and you may direct further inquiries here:

PAYPAL <http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside>

Cookies simply assist in tracking which features you like best and allow content to be customized upon your return, according to prior preferences at that site. At AdServe we may use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our sites.

We do not use cookies to identify, monitor or track any personally identifiable information. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you. We do not merge or associate our cookie information with any personally identifiable information obtained by us or from third parties.

While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with the payment processes are placed by our Payment Services provider. We do not have access to these cookies or any information that they may contain. Please contact the Payment Services provider for more information:

PAYPAL <http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside>

Our site's registration form requires users to supply contact information (such as their name, email, and postal address). This contact information is only used to get in touch with the customer when necessary. It is never sold or shared.

This site contains links to other sites. AdServe is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites once you have left our site. We only link to general audience sites but cannot be responsible for any redirection or content changes over which we have no control. Please contact us immediately if there is a problem with any of our links. [support@adserve.com](mailto:support@adserve.com)

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [help@adserve.com](mailto:help@adserve.com)
